That you are not very, very empathetic.
Because then maybe you can go to work the day after too.
But think that you should work well with the whole psychopathic syndrome.
That you break in empathy and are very impulsive.
And are lying.
You hear that and understand that that combination will burst.
It will knock around that person.
It is an uncontrolled person who is unemployed, manipulative and lying.
That it would be a functioning manager, politician or something else I keep too unlikely.
A fairly common view from the public based on Hollywood
is that psychopaths are particularly smart.
That they would have very high IQ.
Is it really so?
No, this is not what we see in most research studies.
We cannot see that psychopaths are particularly smart when we try to measure IQ in a good way.
We can probably kill that myth it seems.
Thank you for being with us today.
Like if you think what we do is good.
Feel free to comment and do not forget to subscribe.
This is the series about crime where we are seriously talking about crime.
It is important that we give nuanced images of crime.